const pitanjaLvl3 = [
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "M I L K A I C A",
        correctAnswer: "kamilica",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "V A N D A L A",
        correctAnswer: "lavanda",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "N A M E T",
        correctAnswer: "menta",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "M A N I L A",
        correctAnswer: "malina",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "Z E B R A",
        correctAnswer: "breza",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "S T R A H",
        correctAnswer: "hrast",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "G A B R E M",
        correctAnswer: "bagrem",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "B U V A K",
        correctAnswer: "bukva",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "G O N I K",
        correctAnswer: "ginko",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "K O P R A V I",
        correctAnswer: "kopriva",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "R O B",
        correctAnswer: "bor",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "M O S K V A",
        correctAnswer: "smokva",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "P I L A",
        correctAnswer: "lipa",
    },
    {
        question: "Postaviti slova na njihovo ispravno mjesto kako bi se dobio ispravan naziv biljke:",
        letters: "M I L U N",
        correctAnswer: "limun",
    }
];

export default pitanjaLvl3